they got a monkey and a board full of
stocks and they got the monkey to throw
darts to the board and that board
outperformed most managers they survey
that year you can't beat the markets
long term because everybody has access
to the same information my first talk
was tsmc very important lesson I learned
in my very first job working at BCA
research my manager pulled me in and he
was asking me about a bunch of things
and he said look our clients pay us for
our rationale not for our calls you have
a 50/50 chance of getting any call right
here's guess and you can get the call
right for the wrong reason that doesn't
make you right that just makes you lucky
so people pay a lot of money for our
research because they like the way we
structure our thoughts and they like all
the facts and figures and research and
calculations we've done to support the
final conclusion which is by this stock
um the Bank of Canada is projecting
Canada to be in a recession this year
because of the trade War and the Atlanta
fed like I told you is projecting the us
to be in recession
as well so um things aren't looking
great it's possible that Trump is just
using these tariffs as a negotiating
tool nobody that I talked to no
Economist likes tariffs in the idea of
protectionism one time he actually said
this to Trump he said Mr President I
believe you are a free trador at heart
because look at your wives all your
wives are imported from Eastern Europe
I'm a dumbass tell me about
yourself
[Music]
world she the queen of the game stacking
crypto like it's her to fame if you want
success then take a look
away hi David hi
bunny um we've known each other for a
long time a long time yeah how long way
back oh many years I can't remember I
met you two months ago it's like dog
years I meant like dog years right two
months it's like five dog years but yeah
we met at Sailor's party mhm we're
working on something together but we'll
talk about that later right right um I
remember that day at the party I walked
straight up to you guys and I introduced
myself what what inspired you to walk up
to us and I didn't know anybody so I was
like I flew all the way from Taiwan I
might as well just make some friends
right but you could have approached
anybody there but you chose to approach
our group why I know what you want to
hear and I'm going to give that to you
okay cuz you guys look the most
interesting and chill and laid-back and
cool like that's the cool kid area yeah
it was the cool kid area your instincts
are correct and now look at us look who
we are now we're both in Taiwan doing a
podcast um okay so who is Bonnie Chang
for my audience okay wow that's a very
deep question I run a YouTube channel
called Bonnie blockchain so it talks
about um blockchain crypto just to
confirm blockchain is not your last name
right no Bonnie blockchain is a channel
everyone should check out Bonnie
blockchain thank you yeah very good very
good channel so most content are in
Chinese some are in English yeah yeah um
I started it because I saw this Gap in
the market because I was like most um
crypto content are in English
and like a lot of people don't
understand it so I translate all the
content to Chinese type yeah okay why
did you start your channel why yeah
who's interviewing who it's your it's
your show I hijacked it no okay um wait
wait what was your question why did you
start your channel okay it was Co right
so I bought I started buying Bitcoin way
back because I had a really good friend
that was mining I was living in Dubai at
the time and he he's like this guy with
ADHD like he has so many ideas and he
would actually go and do it like one day
it could be like he want to start this
modeling agency and he wants me to
invest or like the next day would be he
wanted you to invest or model invest
okay
invest
yes presumably you could have done both
but anyway continue yes okay um no I
can't do
both multitask you're good at that no no
no no like you have to starve yourself I
gave you a compliment Bonnie just let's
move on
okay um the next day it could be hey I I
want to start this jewelry shop and you
should invest and then the next idea was
hey I started mining in my own bedroom
and I was like are you crazy what do you
mean M and he was telling me about
Bitcoin right yeah and he said you have
to start mining this and that I was like
there's no way this is crazy like what
do you mean you're mining this internet
money mhm but he convinced me to buy
some right so I I was just holding and
it was not that expensive back then I
moved back to Taiwan Co hit and I was
working for a television Company MH and
we're like it was like a variety show
with you know like the Asian style I do
yeah like all the very cute stuff is
this online can we find it yes you no
you cannot okayy and
slip yes you can you can we had
cheerleaders on you know like all these
really pretty girls fortune tellers like
very interesting people on the show but
then later on I was like you know what
for traditional media to run they need a
lot of I I don't want to say clickbait
but they want like oh like this
relationship open relationship with like
five people like all that I don't find
it fulfilling at all like after a while
so I was like I need to start doing my
own
thing and which is investing either
stock or crypto and at the time crypto
was really hot right yeah so I started
researching there weren't many crypto
YouTubers in Chinese so why don't I just
start one m so yeah it's been three
years I know you have questions for me
um but for my American Canadian European
audience watching it's it's a shame that
your channel and I told you this offline
when I saw you last month it's a shame
that your channel was primarily Mandarin
she does a lot of good English
interviews as well um people should
check that out but it's a shame because
I really genuinely think your content is
better than a lot of channels in in the
West for a few reasons one I think you
explain things clearly crypto is not an
easy concept to explain to the Layman
and you do that very well but you don't
dumb it down for people you know you
don't like you don't explain just the
servers you go into depth and you you
analyze things on your own you dissect
other people's research reports uh which
is which is you know you people are lazy
people don't want to reach a 10 page
report from Masari but you do that for
us which is really important and the
flow of the conversation with your
interviews but as well as your solo
presentations I find really good it's
just it's easy to follow and you know I
don't even like watch you I just put it
in the background while I'm doing
something but my my litmus test which is
how good a channel is if if I'm doing
something else and not even watching the
channel Channel I just listen do I learn
something after 15 minutes if the answer
is yes then it's a pretty good channel
so I encourage people to I I don't know
download it translate It audio into or
maybe just watch the interviews yeah
where yeah watch the interviews we'll be
doing a lot of those later but um such a
great compliment thank you well I meant
it it's um people should check out your
channel yeah you speak fluent Chinese I
I fluent is a debatable term
fluent I can order in a restaurant
fluently people don't know you're from
that's a good compliment too considering
that I haven't really spent much time
here I I grew up in Canada but I was
born in taipe okay so you grew up there
you moved there I did I moved to
Vancouver when I was four so your
Chinese should be like four-year-old
level but it's not three-year-old level
three three is there a big difference
between three and four Google trans
helps me out cu I go everywhere and I
you know I translate the text but I can
I can have a conversation we can do this
in Chinese if you
want let's
not and okay your background and your
story can you tell us how you got into
YouTube sure yeah yeah well I I did
Finance at McGill so that's a school in
Canada Montreal I know okay and I um
wanted to work in finance I because
I don't know I liked
money but the study of Finance isn't
just about money which is why I do my
show I'll get to that the study of
finances to understand the world one of
my favorite investment investment
professors in school it was called
applied Investments his name was Ken
Lester and I just love the guy um he
told us that to be a good investor you
have to have worldly knowledge so for
two semesters in a row it was applied
Investments we were given
$250,000 Canadian of the school's
endowment money real money to manage you
had to apply for the class and anyway it
was a we put in groups of four we had to
manage real money and for the entire
semester two semesters actually one
semester and then we had summer break
and then second semester we didn't
really talk about Finance we weren't
taught math or derivatives or
calculations or formulas or theories we
just talked about the world he just gave
us books to read books that had nothing
to do with Finance philosophy like
science he just encouraged us to go
explore whatever it is that we were
interested in outside of our core
studies which was finance and he said
look to be a good investor you have to
put your money into things that you
really understand and so you if you
don't understand anything besides the
theories that were taught to you in the
other core classes like math and
whatever you can't invest in anything
that really got me passionate about
studying Finance because I was studying
everything around me that I enjoyed
learning about so then I did
macroeconomics research right after
school for a firm called BCA research I
did that for 5 years I rotated around I
was an analyst and um I really enjoyed
it after about 5 years somebody reached
out to me on LinkedIn they said hey we
have an opportunity as a producer for
this company that has a media site um
and would you like to would you like to
you know come in for an interview at the
time I was thinking of transitioning
into another job I wasn't sure about
media um I don't have a lot of media of
experience prior to that I worked at a
school newspaper as an editor and that
was about it I really enjoyed that I
managed a team of like 90 people so like
the management part of the job but I
never envisioned myself as a journalist
I wanted to work on Wall Street that was
like my goal so I was like all right
I'll take this for a couple weeks or a
couple years maybe and then I'll put
this on my resume it could be
interesting and then when I apply for an
NBA I might stand out I don't know that
was my thought process so I did that for
two years as a producer my manager at
the time uh the anchor left and then
they were like we don't have anyone to
be on camera like you do it so I
and some other reporters were just
thrown into the spotlight they liked me
so they kept me I did that for 3 years
and then afterward I decided to start my
own channel this was late 2022 I made
the decision to quit and start my own
channel doing similar things but that
channel was more Commodities focused and
I wanted to be more General
Finance because I wanted to expand into
a broader audience and so I started my
own channel in 20123 the David ly report
I couldn't think of anything more
creative I'm not a very creative person
Bonnie I'm Bonnie blockchain
yeah so well okay I think yours
better no you have the word blockchain
in mine's just my own name so that's
basically my story in a nutshell okay um
a lot of questions there sure growing up
what was your relationship with money
you told me this was a chill interview
these are these are really deep
questions okay my relationship with
money um I'll start first that is yeah
yeah tell me what you mean by that as in
like I never really learned how to
invest or like how to budget you know
cuz that's just not how my family worked
MH and so I started investing into like
very conservative Blue Chip stocks after
I started working how old was this this
was were you like
22 I started putting money into like
blue chips yeah I was very conservative
until
crypto and that was
um that's an interesting statement you
just made crypto isn't conservative for
you it's def are you kidding cryp cryp
definitely not okay so I was like the
most conservative investor Blue Chip
tsmc that type you know yeah like big
companies so Taiwanese stocks um um like
US Stocks too but only like mag s like
big one okay 22 this was like I don't
want to review how old you are but this
was a while ago so yeah the Mac 7 back
then is not the same as it is now okay
that's interesting and so you was there
like a mind shift that you had at some
point in your life with your investing
style because you're you're taking on
presumably more risk now you're less
risk averse than maybe you were before
yes which is interesting because people
usually get more risk adverse when they
age okay so I heard a few people told me
hey you are too young to invest in the
most conservative stocks so you were
influenced by pure pressure I was I was
no that that wasn't in that wasn't pure
pressure it was like you are right I can
take a little more risk yeah yeah so I
did that and I got burned a few times
like the reason why I started the
channel is because it's like a journal
of my learning experience as well I'm
learning like everybody else it's just
maybe I spent a little more time doing
this because this is my full-time job
right okay so let me answer your
question growing up I never thought
about money cuz like I was taken care of
I didn't have a job when I was 12 you
know why do I have to care about money I
come home after school there's food on
the table yeah and what is money it's
like yeah the the concept of money
didn't really exist when I until I got
to college and then I had to start
paying my own bills you know
I I I thought of money in the sense when
I was growing up you asked me when I was
growing up I thought of about money the
sense of how much it could buy like toys
and things that I could relate to at the
time
right um I was like really into music
actually my dream was to become a
musician that didn't work out and so now
I'm doing
podcasts so I I um I thought about money
in the sense of how much it would cost
to buy a violin or a piano this was till
when maybe my mid M I was taking some
like entry-level economics classes in
high school
no way yeah they offered some entrylevel
economic classes and then this was like
actually college level they gave it to
us in high school and I started reading
about the economy and I understood I
think that's when I first started to
understand that money is not an ends to
just buy things it's and it's it's a
means to move everything in our Liv so
um wait you learned that in high school
it's something that I thought about
right because the flow of capital and
the flow of money is is is is deeper
than simply what you want to buy with it
but anyway we can get into that later uh
no I want to get into it now see this is
why I like Bonnie she doesn't let me off
the
hook when I'm a kid and I want to buy
something it costs me I don't know $10
to go buy some candy in a movie store at
a at a movie theater okay where did that
$10 come from came from my mom and my
dad where do they get their money from
they got it from their jobs where do
they get their jobs from they got it
from because the economy is functional
and capitalism works and so they're able
to have the opportunity to grow their
own wealth um where does income come
from these are kinds of Concepts that I
was not exposed to before I started
really thinking about it um we had like
stock portfolio like simulations and I
remember uh the first time I did this
the assignment was you have one month
you can buy whatever you want and the
person with the highest returns in the
class win some sort of prize I can't
remember what the prize was like a grade
or something and I I know I did I was
like I called my mom's friend who was a
broker I said what what what do I do uh
I I don't know what to
buy don't tell my eighth grade teacher
but anyway he um he said well you have
one month so you probably want something
that's really volatile so he just made
me buy oil Futures so at 8 I was 12
years 13 years old at the time that is
crazy so I was like okay what are oil
Futures he was like well you know what
oil is right you go to the gas station
you buy gas okay and then like this this
is he explains this to a 13-year-old
quite well uh Futures are just
instruments that allow you to buy things
at you know you can not buy the physical
you can buy things that are traded on
markets so anyway so I didn't wi it it
it went down a lot my relationship with
my relationship with money was always
one of apathy I would say and just
ignorance until I took classes in
University and you started making your
own money I think that's I started
making my own money after University I
got my first job after
University wait so okay this is very
hard for me to understand for me I have
to earn my own money to really
understand what $1,000 means this means
this much amount of work or like or the
amount of time you spent making time or
effort you put in because when you take
money from your parents it means nothing
it's just a
number well at least in my case like I
start understanding money my mom would
be work for it when I was a kid she
would be like dude chores so people were
talking about this idea of bringing up
kids like that what you're doing
actually when you're doing that is
you're training them to work for other
people as opposed to training them to be
entrepreneurs so my my my my parents are
pretty conservative when it comes to
like you know making money actually
that's kind of hypocritical because my
mom had her own business but she always
was like she wanted me to take the safer
route which is to work for somebody else
which is the opposite of what I'm doing
now but so when you train your kids to
like earn money through chores and
whatever tasks they give you what you're
really doing is instilling them a
responsibility to work for somebody else
and so you're training them to be in the
workforce whereas you could have been
like hey here's $10 where here's $100 go
grow that right here go buy some
lawnmower equipment and go down the
that's what I would do with my kids I
would be I would give them like $200 go
buy whatever you want I would teach them
like if you buy this let's say it's a
lawnmower you could in theory make x
amount of money with that piece of
equipment if you go down the street and
you know you solicit your neighbors to
go cut their lawns so it's a different
approach but I was given an allowance
when I was a kid because my mother made
me do the dishes and you know clean the
room and all that kind of stuff so I
don't know I don't know how it worked
with you but this reminded me of
something so I used to travel to us a
lot and you know a lot of American
airports they the trolley you actually
need to put in like I I don't remember
$7 or8 $9 to get the trolley what
trolley like the trolley for luggage $8
yeah it's not what currency you're
looking at US Dollars okay anyway yeah
like seven or nine I can't remember so
but people will actually leave their
trolleys everywhere after they don't
need it anymore mhm and they'll have
this staff collecting them and put it
back and everybody has to just pay so
what we like my dad used to make us do
is when we were waiting for a flight
like we're there early he would just ask
us to go collect trolleys and like sell
them for five did you understand as a
kid like okay I if I if I profited $5
let's say yeah I could buy something
with it like did it mean something to
you did you have like an urge with a
child to like buy things no no no no I
so you so you didn't have a need for
money no but that was like an
interesting way of teaching kids I think
think yeah I don't know if it's legal
but I I don't I don't think it's a law
against I don't think it's a law against
it technically it's child labor but so
if you're under 16 you're breaching
child labor laws I think everybody was
happy they're like oh instead of
spending seven now I'm spending five
right it's great right yeah why were you
investing when you were 22 and I'll
answer the same question why was I
investing yeah I don't know I really
don't know like there was just money
sitting in the bank doing nothing
right you could have bought stuff with
it you could have wasted your money I
bought my stuff and I still have some
money left and it was just sitting there
I don't need it I mean you were old
enough to understand that if you had
bought stocks like you did you could
have lost money right so you did take
some risk I I mean if you wanted zero
risk you could have bought treasuries
you could have bought money market funds
you could have just collected at low
yields right you could but you chose to
buy equities right I don't know if I was
thinking that much okay just just
because you just bought things you went
understood and liked yeah yeah okay my
first talk was
tsmc because you liked till now yeah
yeah and you held it you never sold it
no okay no wow
um why did I want to buy stocks that's a
good question I don't know it's just
because like I said I never really
thought about how money worked until I
start started really studying it I used
to look at it in terms of how much I can
buy like oh like right now I can buy a
car and later I can buy this I can buy
that like my net worth can afford a
certain type of thing but then like you
said it could like later on you realize
money is just a tool to move things or
like to help you with things I don't
look at it as what can I buy with this
instead I look at it as what can I do
with this like who can I hire or mhm
like what type of production can I
upgrade and all that yeah yeah yeah your
your relationship with money completely
changes once you start running your own
business oh yes well at least for me I
don't think about money as what do I buy
with $10 I think about how do I grow my
business with $10 everything I do
there's there's this just add value to
my to my company and ultimately my net
worth and there's I have a I have a
budget for things that don't do anything
for me like there's just fun and the
rest of it is like does itat the ad
value long term right it's I think about
money as everything I do is an
investment into my own company I've
disclosed as many times in other
interviews I own zero public Securities
right now oh I have some Bitcoin and
ethereum and salana that I bought years
ago I never sold it I don't trade it I
just leave it there um does it stress
you out no I don't care right I really
don't care like it's just there and H
yeah
I am not invested in any companies right
now because I'm still in the startup
phase so every dollar that I have is
invested in my own company so I am
invested I'm just invested in the David
ly company because I can I have more
confidence in my own Roi if I know that
I a hire somebody or you know expand
someone's salary or buy some equipment
or invest in a trip or whatever I can
reasonably estimate how much return
short-term and medium-term and longterm
I could make from that investment
whereas I have no idea what tsmc is
going to do next month do you I don't
you're speculating whereas I'm investing
there's a difference okay stop attacking
me okay do do you feel that way I feel
like I'm being attacked there's nothing
wrong with speculating um but every time
we buy a stock we're speculating I'm I'm
not just singling out every time you buy
Nvidia or anything you're definitionally
speculating um Benjamin Grahams book who
was the mentor of Warren gr uh Warren
Buffett and the intelligent investor and
I think chapter two he outlined the
difference between speculating and
investing and he a very simple
definition it's just the degree of risk
that you take if believe that you know
for certain because I don't know you
have Insider information that tsmc is
going to have good quarterly earnings
next quarter you're not really
speculating you're investing but you
don't have that information I have
information as to how I'm going to do my
company is going to perform in the next
quarter so that's that's the difference
between for me investing and speculating
um I'm investing in my own company now
and then as soon as it grows big enough
I'll diversify into other things so that
you know it's not just dependent on the
cash flows from one company the tsmc
example ex Le though how I look at it is
you get a bunch of smartest people on
Earth working on something that is
benefiting the world mhm and you are
owning a piece of it I have a piece of
ice stuck in my mouth
H Karma she's of for attacking me I'm
waiting for your Counterattack because I
know that's what you're going to do it's
not an attack but what what I how I see
this is well there you own a piece of of
the smartest people working on the
smartest product sure right I can work
on my own company but I also want to be
a part of that that's awesome absolutely
like being a part of something you
really trust or believe in right but
this is that like tsmc but then earlier
I said a lot of crypto are not that safe
or not
conservative is because after Bitcoin
ethereum Sal there was a period of time
I started investing in a lot of projects
I did not really understand
and that is I think a
mistake mhm because why are you called
Bonnie blockchain and not bnny Finance
or bunny money or you know I talk about
finance and stuff other things that's
exactly why I'm asking you this because
your com your channel was pretty
Diversified in the scope you talk about
Chad gbt talk about I actually it's
interesting story because I I told you
this right my cousin yeah um he watched
your show and he has nothing to do with
Finance so she's pretty well known in
Taiwan so she he was like oh wow you're
meeting Bonnie I watched her show nice
anyway um you talk about AI a lot so I'm
just curious why you branded yourself as
a blockchain channel it's because it's
too late to change my name no it's not
it literally takes 5 seconds it's a
conscious decision so I want to get into
that you decided not to change it now
why um just because I thought it was too
late the moment I was like hey I'm might
want to change it to something else I
was like it was already at 150k not a
lot but I was like there are a bunch of
people 150k subscribers oh no oh no it's
too late it it is too late as like I was
like there was a a group of people that
are used to you being called that I
don't know you're absolutely right yeah
like you're trying to make me invest in
my own company sell my own stock all of
my stocks and change my channel name I'm
not giving you Financial advice but you
do what you
want yeah I thought about it mm MH mhm
but this channel is still mainly crypto
I see like when there's a crypto crash I
talk about it when there's not all
Finance people want to know everything
that's going on is there a crypto crash
going on right now you think the economy
how is it doing I like this one she
answers my questions with a question yes
the economy is doing all right it's the
Atlanta fed GDP now tracker which is um
a forecast of the GDP from the Atlanta
fed is now in negative territory for the
first time in many many years so it went
from positive 2% GDP growth next
Quarter Two readings ago to negative 1.5
to negative 2.8 how is that good that's
not good M it's um it's because trade
data came in recently and that was
really really bad manufacturing data
came in really bad so it's possible that
if the data improves next next month um
it'll go back up to positive but right
now the forecast is a sharp contraction
in the economy next quarter
uh the markets think so which is why all
week everything's been down and uh just
yesterday Trump announced tariffs on
Canada Mexico well he didn't announce
them he put them into effect and I'm
from Canada so uh our prime minister
trudo
immediately uh used retaliatory tariffs
25% on us Imports um the Bank of Canada
is projecting Canada to be in a
recession this year because of the trade
War and the fed like I told you is
projecting the us to be in recession as
well so um things aren't looking great
it's possible that Trump was just using
these tariffs as a negotiating tool so
uh we'll see if he resends them and
takes them back after a while but right
now if we're pricing an information that
comes in now it's it's looking like
probably a contraction I've talked to
many people who have friends who just
got laid off this week because uh
because their companies know that their
sales are going to be down you're
talking about Canada I'm talking about
Canada and the US right
now what Trump is doing and I had an
interesting conversation with a guest
recently about this what Trump is doing
is he's turning David Ricardo's theory
of comparative advantage upside down the
theory the theory of comparative
advantage is that when there is global
trade everyone is better off because you
are trading with a partner by producing
something that you're better at
producing at versus a partner who's not
as good at producing that thing so if
I'm better at producing silk and you're
better at producing computers I will
trade silk with your computers but now
we're turning that completely upside
down because we're putting trade
barriers between that so now I don't
want to trade my silk for your computers
because I'd rather it's
probably less expensive for me to just
make my own computers so what's going to
happen is we're going to push or Trump
is going to probably push a lot of other
Industries around the world and other
countries around the world to really
start developing their own Industries
whereas before they traded with the US
China for example if the US imposes even
stricter tariffs restrictions on Chinese
trade instead of the Chinese buying us
chips they will just be forced to buy
their own longterm it's actually a
losing proposition for the
US so nobody that I've talked to no
Economist likes tariffs and the idea of
protectionism you're just objectively
better off without any trade barriers
imagine if you were Trump why would you
be doing this while he said this he
wants he wants to use this as leverage
right he wants wants to negotiate other
terms and conditions with his trading
partners and then he would probably take
the tars off last month for example he
announced tariffs on Canada
Canada uh he wanted Canada to have a
fent noar which is somebody in charge of
you know um overseeing the distribution
of fenel into the US he wanted 10,000
additional Patrol officers On the Border
he wanted um a host of other things and
Canada agreed and he took them off the
table well he take it off the table he
postponed it by a month yes now that
month is up so uh I think if more terms
are met then it's possible that these
tffs will be taken off I talked to Art
laugher about this who was given the
presidential medal of freedom by Trump
in 2017 M or it 2018 I can't remember
but in his last term and art laugher was
the um he worked for the Nixon
Administration and he was part of the
Council of policy advisers for Reagan so
he's very well
vers in government he believes that
Trump is a free Trader at heart and he's
just using this as negotiation and
laugher had a good story one time he
actually said this to Trump he said Mr
Mr President I believe you are a free
trador at heart because look at your
wives all your wives are imported from
Eastern Europe so he did not he he did
say that um apparently Trump did not
appreciate the
joke okay so yeah I mean his wives are
imported so I don't think you actually
like trade restrictions he said so yeah
cuz he's a business guy M so he should
know all this right yeah I mean look he
understands trade and he understands
deal making I think I've read his book
when I was a well one of his books when
I was a uh 12th grade I was in anyway I
read I read one of his books in high
school and he likes to negotiate with
people uh using like I would say
unconventional methods um he wrote in
his book that he
one of the deals he made in real estate
in New York because he was a real estate
developer before President and he really
wanted a building mhm the guy wouldn't
sell it to him eventually they gave him
a really high price he didn't want to
pay that price so what he did was he
started slandering that building and
convinced everybody else around him that
that building sucks and that they
shouldn't buy it so eventually he drove
the price down and because nobody wanted
it and then when the price was low
enough he picked it up
so uh he plays hard ball when he
negotiates and I think he's using that
on the international
Arena so can I say the economy doesn't
look good now but this could just be for
the moment I think the economy is still
strong right now but the markets are
projecting
weakness but then when everybody
believes in something that's going to
happen really Bonnie you don't think so
no no I don't think so really but in
this case we're talking about what the
markets believe and the markets believe
that the economy is going to be worse
yes I mean whe whether or not I believe
it see that's the thing with investing
right that's why there's a market if you
believe one thing and somebody else
believes another you trade if everyone
believes one thing there wouldn't be a
market because everyone would be selling
and there would be no buyers or everyone
would be buying and there would be
nothing to sell um if you think that the
market is wrong and that there isn't
going to be weakness you should be
buying the dip right now I am there you
go Bonnie the bull
but I don't know if I call it buying the
dip I just constantly buy your dollar
cost average no I just buy when it's
relatively lower I will invest longterm
so the fact that it's 320 or 330 right
now doesn't matter to me like if I
really believe in a company and I know
I'm going to hold it for the next 10
years it doesn't really matter if it's
like 300 or 310 or 3 50 that's a right
approach if you're a long-term holder
yes so am I buying the dip yes I am but
is it because I think it's going to go
up short term not necessarily MH yeah I
mean it's not even that much of a dip
we're still near all-time highs for the
S&P yes what about crypto what about
crypto bunny you okay you hold Bitcoin
ethereum and salana yeah instead of
stocks so I I don't know what salana is
trading at today I really I haven't
looked at it I don't know see that my
point is I have I don't it's just there
um and I'm not trading it I'm not doing
anything with it I just have it so but
why crypto why not a stock because you
say you want to invest I did I I traded
stocks when I was in my 20s and I
realized I'm not a good Trader so I
stopped doing that why weren't you an
investor cuz with Bitcoin it seems like
you're because I didn't have patience I
think it's a personality thing at the
time I wanted
to you know I was hanging out with a
bunch of like you know they the DJ
Finance Bros and like I literally went
to the bank I got a line of credit cuz I
was like 21 22 I just started working I
have money I got a line of credit from a
bank and they're like why do you need it
I said I literally sit this with a
straight face I said I'm trading stocks
which is what what you should tell a
bank when you're getting a line of
credit by the way and the adviser was
just like okay how old are you 21 do you
have experience
no okay um what stocks are you buying I
don't know yet okay approve
D it was approved it was approved wow I
got a few th it wasn't a lot it was a
few thousand Canadian and I used it all
on trading options specifically covered
calls so a covered call is you buy
something and then you sell the option
the cover call um I never I never sold
naked calls and then that got too boring
for me so I just stopped doing covered
calls I just started trading options I
just started buying like naked calls and
puts and I lost everything and um I was
like you know what I'm not really good
at this
and um my friends were like why don't
you buy something you know hold it
longterm and I did I held it for me that
back then 3 months was longterm I made
like 10% on something I was like that's
enough time to scalp so I just didn't
have patience if I held if I had held
those positions until now I would have
made a lot more I should have been like
you yeah but you're holding crypto so
that is true so why am I holding crypto
I bought it because I was covering it at
the time so it was just 2020 I was a
late adopter I I never bought Bitcoin
early because I never really understood
it we can talk about that but um I
started for my job as a journalist as an
anchor I started interviewing a lot of
people in crypto so I was like I need to
educate myself and the only way to do
that is to buy it and have skin in the
game so I bought it and then it did
force me to look into it a little bit
more um and then there was a big
downturn as you know in 2022 I sold some
of it in
2021 not because I knew there was a
crash coming I didn't I just you know I
I made some profit and I took profits
that
and the rest there but the only reason I
bought crypto is so I could understand
it more right now I don't I don't really
what happens to it so you don't care
that's very interesting like I would
leave it there I don't check the price
every day but I would care if it
crash not that it will worry me but I
will care I'm I'm not a hedge fund
Bonnie I mean I'm not a I'm not a crypto
fund right I don't like it's not my main
business true so if my main business
crashes I would care if the David Lyn
stock crashes I would care but if salana
goes down 50% which it did after FTX I
think more you know yes did I go down
yeah but like I just did I buy more no
did I sell no I just left it alone and I
did something else with my life and I
think that allowed me to sleep safely
cuz you know a lot of people leverage
themselves to the point where it's like
okay well if it goes down what do I do
with my life oh yeah you should never
put that kind of stress on yourself MH
for any kind of investment mhm like your
net worth should not be your determinant
of your personal happiness and life
satisfaction yes yeah it's interesting
what what you just said cuz I talk about
blockchain and crypto right
so I mean I started trading meme coins
for a while this was like probably a
year or two years ago and that was
probably one of the worst decision I've
ever made but no because you learned
from yes yes the reason why I wanted to
start trading meme coins is because I
need to understand what everyone else is
doing right so you can talk about it I
don't like to talk about things that I
don't understand I don't like to pretend
that I understand it right so that was
bad like financially that was bad but
it's a good
lesson so like you said my focus should
be on the main business instead of like
all the Investments like so later on I
kind of pivot my investment strategy
into I'm buying all the things that I
don't really need to look at every day
okay so things that aren't very volatile
well comparative to relative to like uh
meme coin yeah yeah mem coins they a lot
of them they survive for 24 hours so I
think we're on the same page I think you
and I both bought things for similar
reasons because we want to learn not
because I expected to get rich from it
right no no no that's a very different
mentality because if you wanted to get
rich off mean coins you would have you
have approached it differently mhmh yeah
you would have allocated different
positions you would have looked at it
differently you would have traded more
frequently whatever right but you
approached it from a learning angle I
can understand that yeah and I got
burned David well what did we both
learn I got burned with options you got
burned with meme coins yeah so here we
are doing a podcast terrible we could
have done a we could have done a a a
hedge fund but now but no we didn't
hey your channel grew very fast you
started coming from you a year ago right
no I started in
2023 okay it's been exactly two years
okay two years Yes actually yeah what
day are we yeah two years yeah how' you
do that what is different from other
channels I don't know I don't know
what's different is it because you're
funny or is it because you don't blink
do you think I'm funny kabani no why do
you keep laughing at my jokes
is it because you ask very smart
questions is it because you upload very
frequently what is it I'm very lucky to
work with a lot of really smart guests
the guests make the show people don't I
I like to think people don't watch for
me they they watch for my guests MH yeah
I do upload more frequently than I think
other channels in the space I do like
one two a day well I'm I'm in Taiwan I'm
half on vacation so I'm doing only one a
day now that's still a lot kind of and
and I do that just to keep it going
I don't think people understand how hard
it is to upload that many videos yeah
you just have to sacrifice sleep and a
lot of other things yeah or like
interviews they think you really just
sit down and chat with people but no you
prep yeah absolutely so how do you prep
for an interview what did you do before
this interview I I I researched Bonnie
Chang oh that's terrible no no I learned
a lot no okay let's say you're about to
interview like um
expert in some fi that you're not
familiar with sure what do you do okay
well it depends who it is so if it's
somebody I know well I would just ask
him about this week's or today's market
movement let's say he's a Trader or an
investor and we just talk about the news
so my process is I get up every morning
I have a really good team my producer
helps me with topics every morning and
we just look at what's driving the
markets that day and then that would be
the program for maybe a Trader I have on
later in the day if it's somebody like
okay I just had I'll give you a recent
example I don't know Arthur Hayes I just
interviewed him you know Arthur Hayes
bitm co-founder I just interviewed him
last week great interview so we spent a
couple days just researching um his
views we went through his Twitter
profile we went through his tweets uh we
pulled up some crypto news and events
that maybe he could talk about like we
talked about biped for example um he
tweeted about the ethereum roll back so
we talked about that um we talked about
Perpetual Futures because he's the
founder he's a creator of that um so you
just kind of look at what the guy's done
and and and it's like preparing for any
kind of conversation like you go on a
date right do you do like no thinking
whatsoever same kind of concept right
you have an idea of what you want to get
out of that conversation and you just
think about I don't okay well don't you
just go on a
date look not everybody is as naturally
gifted as you some of us have to prepare
okay what do you stand in front of a
mirror and be like hi I'm David lint
like Howes maybe I should do that no but
I just think about it's the same it's
the same concept and the point I'm
making is that it's the same concept for
any conversation whether you're doing a
professional interview or you're on a
date or you're going to meet your mom or
whatever it's like if you have an idea
yeah you have an idea of what you want
to get out of that interaction and so
you kind of I reverse engineer the
result by thinking about the types of
questions I would ask or the types of
conversations I would like to have and
so knowing that what is my process well
if let's say Okay I want to interview
Arthur Hayes I want to get his Bitcoin
views then looked up all the Articles
he's written about his Bitcoin views or
you know what does he think about the
Bitcoin strategic Reserve well it so
happens that he wrote an article on
medium not too long but long not too
long criticizing the Bitcoin strategic
reserve for a lot of reasons and he
talked about some other things he had a
$1 million Bitcoin call for I think
later this year he actually correctly
called 100,000 Bitcoin for this year you
know these are all things that I wanted
to talk to him about and so I looked it
up so I'm just using him as an example
the same process for
everybody but that like whatever he's
talking about you are pretty familiar
with cuz you are also a Bitcoin investor
Le let's talk about like gold you do
talk about gold bonds and all that right
yeah do are you investing in those
things no I have nothing besides Bitcoin
ethereum and Sala right so how do you
ask real estate real
estate right how do you ask those
questions it well it doesn't it's not
dependent on whether or not invested I'm
just you know do you understand it like
for example I hope I do do you I hope so
do I'll let the audience decide let's be
specific so let's say gold for example
right it's um I've covered gold enough
over my career to understand the drivers
so US dollar real interest rates
inflation expectations um Central Bank
demand buying from retail investors
buying from institutional investors
Chinese demand is really big so these
are all topics that we can touch on for
that one particular asset class
and so I just newsing topics so every
asset class has I would say macro
drivers that are more important for that
asset class and so I just find news for
those variables what is one guest that
you really like having on Bonnie Chang
oh my God
no she's gonna cut that out isn't she no
like surprisingly good or you weren't
exp surprisingly good no one really
surprised me because I went into the
bookings knowing who they were like I
knew exactly how good they were going to
be um I think a few people may have
changed the way I looked at things who
I'll give you some examples so one of my
school Idols was Eugene F who was the
Nobel Laurette in 2013 um he was awarded
the Nobel Prize for his work that he
mainly did in the 70s so it was like a
long time ago and he was one of the
people most closely associated with the
efficient market hypothesis
which is the theory that markets are
efficient and there's different forms of
efficiency there strong medium and weak
form um it means that the market
participants all investors in the market
have access to the same information
basically what he's saying is you can't
beat the markets long term because
everybody has access to the same
information in order to beat the markets
you have to have an information
Advantage which is strong form efficient
which means you have to have Insider
info basically uh but but for everybody
else we see the news we see prices we
see whatever it's information that
everybody else has you might get lucky
one year but averaged it out over a
period of many years or decades you
would not be outperforming the market is
his theory okay I mean I've studied it
but listening to him explain really
challenged me my existence like why am I
doing my job if the theory holds that
you can't really beat the markets and
all I'm doing is asking people how to
beat the markets really when you think
about it but do you really believe that
that you can't beat the market well see
the fund managers I interview don't
believe that right do I believe it see
see I'm not a professional investor so I
don't know I don't know if I believe
that or not he has enough proof and
evidence that he's formulated this
Theory a lot of people disagree with him
he want the Nobel price for his proof I
would like to think yes we have access
to all the same information but most
people will not the people that he's not
saying is impossible to be the markets
he's saying the people that do have
asymmetric information right interesting
if you're somebody who doesn't over the
long term you will just perform about
the same as the market if you're good
and in fact most funds lose most
actively managed funds lose money yes
over the long term MH there was a book
I'm not sure if you read this David
conman Thinking Fast and Slow we had to
read that in college he was using an
example um there was a they got a monkey
and a board full of stocks you got the
monkey to throw darts to the board and
that board outperformed most managers
they surveyed that year I'm not saying
most managers are not as good as a
monkey but you know I feel like the
traditional Finance landscape is people
using all these big words selling you
things you don't understand in Chinese
we call it G right all the product that
are tall huge and up there like you know
all the terms they use they just look
very professional just to really make
money off the product you buy they're
trying to sell you something they might
not even believe in that is possible
right yeah
and I don't know it's like I I feel like
YouTube or like channels like yours kind
of help people more
people um learn about all these things
that used to be like those mysterious
like things that are very far away like
you don't really get economists talking
about their views
before YouTube how how do you even talk
like hear from Arthur Hayes people like
you know or Michael sailor they won't
they they don't go on TV and tell people
what they think but with YouTube and
channels like yours people have access
to these type of information instantly
and I feel like a lot of like big names
right now they're trying to explain
things in a way they want people to
understand them they used to not want
that I think you're right that's where
channels like you and me come in so you
take information from somebody else
who's like a big name or whoever and
then you filter that and then you
explain it in a way that people can
understand yeah because maybe not
everybody understands what Michael
sailor is trying to say but you explain
it uh in a way that people do so that's
that's the value that's the alpha that
you add as a channel it's not so much
that you have insid or info or maybe you
do it's that you are able to educate the
audience whereas Maybe
they haven't either paid attention to a
topic before where they just don't
understand it and they don't really care
to listen to it
m so the hedge fund example I feel like
right now people don't see hedge funds
or like those traditional Finance people
in the way they used to look at them
before which way is that which which is
you know they always outperform the
market and they always know what they're
talking about they always you know what
I mean like I sometimes I feel like
people you talk to they are an expert so
they have to have an opinion even when
they don't know what's
happening but for you to be presentable
on camera or in front of an audience you
need
to believe in
something you can't say I don't know I
think for most people I don't know do
you feel like there's a lot of fake
confidence out there yes yeah yes people
who they're fake gurus they're all over
YouTube yes
that's an interesting topic on its own
yes you know how do you differentiate
yourself from a fake Guru who's selling
a course or whatever I just say I don't
know when I don't know right yeah like I
don't want to pretend to be the person
that oh yeah I know what I'm doing I
make however many millions using this
trading method you don't rent a private
jet and post pictures of a joke yeah I
know you
don't I like
people just being the M themselves and
like I like people who are the same on
and off camera well let me ask you this
question why do you think people watch
our show I don't consider myself an
expert you said you don't consider
yourself an expert I think you're an
expert in crypto But but so why should
people care about us if we're not
experts because like you said we do the
homework for them okay and the fact that
we spend more time on it maybe you're
better than or I am better than the
average person that doesn't really pay
attention to it but I cannot say oh I'm
like I know what's going to happen I
don't but I have an opinion well if I
have an opinion then it's based on all
the research that I've done it's not
like oh I I I can tell with all these
like charts and lines and all that like
I come up with this conclusion and
everyone should just buy in this what we
know from this is that Bonnie is not a
technical traitor definitely not no no I
don't you don't you're not you're not
interested you just don't think it works
or why I have no time to do everything
yeah yeah and Technical trading is the
antithesis it's the opposite of what you
yeah do it's a it's a different
philosophy because you want to be a part
of a society if you want to call that
the tsmc society you want to be a part
of that you want to own the equity you
want to feel like you're you're invested
in a group of really smart people
technical analysis is the opposite of
that a lot of technical traders do not
know what they're trading they don't
care they don't care it's a ticker and
they look at it and they just see lines
and charts uh and they look at the
candles and and they make forecast based
on whatever the numbers are they don't
really care what the underlying Equity
or you know fundamentals are so it's the
exact opposite of what you do that
sounds a lot cooler though does it yeah
it's like okay you don't want to be cool
then bunny no I don't okay I don't I
think you're pretty cool as you are you
don't need to thank you try
harder why do you think people watch you
well like I said I don't think they
watch me they watch my guests you don't
think they watch you if you replace me
with AI that was sufficiently Advanced
that could ask my questions that have
the same banter as a guest they would
still watch the channel that's what I
believe you can say that about everybody
I just do the
homework you know you can replace me
with an AI That's fine you have a really
high engagement rate though I don't know
why how you do it because you don't post
let's talk about growth for your channel
bnie cuz you're growing really fast when
I met met you December 31st M end of the
year you were at 249,000 subscribers oh
my God how do you even know I don't even
know what do you mean I just I you
showed me your channel and I remember oh
wow okay and you're at what 278 today I
don't know you're at 278 today thank you
so that's uh
299,000 subscribers gained in in uh 60
days that's yeah that's really good that
other words that's 15% of your base
grown in 60 days what's interesting to
me is that you don't post as often as me
you have like three four posts a day or
a week rather a week sometimes even one
so the engagement rate of your videos is
really really high meaning people who
watch those one or two videos a week
they subscribe or they'll comment you
have like thousands of comments per
video and you just sit there and you
talk like you don't like you don't play
with a camel you don't
building like I I honestly like I'm
impressed how do you do it thank you I
don't know I I talk about things that I
would find interesting okay and not just
like the news itself sometimes like you
get a market crash or you know a big
event but what I want to know is what
happened why and has it happened before
what does it really mean instead of like
oh the market crashed and see I think
this is why why you have a community
because you talk about things that you
find interesting and so if other people
find it interesting as well this is this
is a this is another philosophy if you
think it's interesting then you probably
will find other people that will think
it's interesting as well and then you're
building like a bonding Community you
know it's like a lot of people watch you
because you have shared interests so um
I'm just really impressed at how fast
you're growing given how little you're
publishing I would love to publish
more okay why what what do you mean why
why do you want to publish more I feel
like there a lot more topics that we can
cover but it's just like what's stopping
you
short-handed okay well that's a to that
that's topic for another day this is why
you should collaborate with me
more yeah I feel like for example all
the AI stuff why did I start talking
about it because I'm interested in it
right I would love to learn more but I'm
not an engineer like I'm not a tech bro
I don't really understand so I study it
and it's like do you stud how do you
study it I spend time just reading and
trying out new tools you know all that
there must be something you're doing
that is
really making the audience stick like
your retention I don't I haven't seen
your stats but your retention rate must
be really high like the audience must
watch you from the beginning to at least
three quter of your video I'm sure this
one will be high retention right because
of my hair or because
okay have I blinked enough for you I
just think that that you're doing
something and I I don't know what it is
I'm trying to ask you like you're doing
something that cuz you probably think
about this every day how do I make the
audience stick to at least 50% of my
video I don't think about that you don't
no I think about that every video I do
see I should but what I think about more
is how do I get them to come in like
click as in not clickbait but you have
to let them it's like a shop right so
you're a thumbnail and your headline yes
so I constantly change my thumbnails a
test and all that how do you get your
thumbnail ideas from I just draw on a
paper and show it to my editor yeah okay
it's not nothing too like fancy yeah
what I do is just in front of a computer
I'm like okay well David Lynn should be
here I should be there and his eyes has
to meet my eyes and you know all that
yeah he should blink every once in a
while yes yes do you think about your
thumbnail before you make the video no I
do that I Mr Beast does that yeah one of
the people I work with who was an
investor of mine used to work for Mr
Beast so he taught me that M he said you
should start thinking about your
thumbnail even what is our thumbnail
this is your show bunny I I don't want
to influence you okay if it was yours
yeah what would the thumbnail be well
your face I mean
yeah I feel like it should just be your
face I mean it's like an attractive face
is should just no text oh my goodness
that's a terrible thing thumbnail maybe
a bit of text but I don't I I don't know
I don't I have to think about this I
don't know what my thumbnail could be
because this this is on a market related
conversation but how do you know how the
conversation would go beforehand because
a lot oftimes just like you you script
out your conversations you sent me a
bunch of questions I send you a bunch of
questions but we're talking about a lot
of other questions that are not on the
questions Winston Churchill famous quote
World War
Two why are you laughing okay okay he
said he said plans are us
but preparations are indispensable MH
mhm I like that so just because you have
a list of questions you're not following
them I know you're not but the fact that
you've taken the time to think about it
has made you mentally prepare for this
conversation right but what I'm saying
is for thumbnails it's really hard
because sometimes we could talk about
gold and then like a more interesting
topic came up and that is better for the
thumbnail sure I would use that instead
yes absolutely yeah yeah so I I'll see
what the THB I'll have to watch this and
see what the thumbnail should be yeah so
my I I look at it as a shop how do I get
people to come in first and of course I
put a lot of work in the editing and
like the script and everything so I
would hope that I have the confidence
that people would stay but first they
need to come in to see hey this is good
mhm I'm telling you they do stay or at
least me and like I don't even watch
your stuff like I watch it and
like my Mandarin isn't that good I don't
understand everything but you know I
just it's also like an exercise think
how much do I understand so 50% that's
good oh thanks cuz there are a lot of
like big words and stuff you know yeah
stop using big words Bonnie let the ABCs
like me understand more but I just I I
feel like I the things I do understand
it's like oh I didn't even think about
that it's like I now I should look into
that more as a content creator it's like
you know that's a good idea what's one
secret how do you keep people watching
your stuff if it's a secret bunny I'm
not telling you or anybody else oh no
come on man what's one secret you mean
what like how do you maybe how do you
structure the conversation I start with
the most important topic that I think
people would click on
so it varies right let's suppose we're
doing a conversation with an inter with
an investor today or a Trader right now
uh Dow's down 500 points today so let's
start with that I always put myself in
the shoes of my audience they're people
who just want to understand what's going
on with their money they want to learn
how to make money they want to
understand the market so okay well
Market's crashing today let's start with
that let's not talk about anything else
let's just talk about what's driving the
new cycle which is the markets are
tanking so what do we do my first
question is okay is this the start of a
bigger bare Market what do I care about
if I'm an investor right I want to know
if this is going to be even worse or is
this the end so now my guest was saying
well you know I think this is just a
kind of a by the dip scenario okay why
so now we understand is logic actually a
very important lesson I learned in my
very first job working at BCA research
my manager pulled me in and he was
asking me about a bunch of things and he
said look our clients pay us for our
rationale not for our calls because
anybody could you have a 5050 chance of
getting any call right you just guess
and you can get the call right for the
wrong reason that doesn't make you right
it just makes you lucky so people pay a
lot of money for our research because
they like the way we structure our
thoughts and they like all the facts and
figures and research and calculations
we've done to support the final
conclusion which is by this stock or
whatever could be wrong but and they
have been wrong many times but they
still have a lot of clients have you
ever interviewed people where you just
look at that person you're like I cannot
upload this
interview I feel like you're about to
share some stories no I've done that I
no I mean I wouldn't have interviewed in
the first place there are a few
interviews that I've done that I haven't
uploaded um because it hasn't turned out
the way I wanted it to um and sometimes
you know you try to pull the information
out it's like it again it goes back to
do I find this information interesting
as a viewer and the answer is really
really no then I wouldn't do it but it
very rarely happens Bonnie because um
I've uploaded 792 videos as of today
since 2023 wow and I only have maybe
less than five cases where that's
happened so is it because it's not
interesting enough it's always my job to
pick out information that's interesting
and in a 30-minute conversation of let's
say one answer isn't good or you know
it's not interesting I'll just cut it
out there's always something interesting
in a conversation I find so there's
there's always something that's
salvageable and if the guest is not
saying something interesting it's that's
my failure as a host to bring out the
interesting information because these
are people that are really smart that I
talk to so there's always something to
talk about and not everybody is good in
front of a camera so people get
you not everybody is very good at
articulating thoughts like the really
really smart people that I've
interviewed are like rman they can't
talk very well but they're super smart
so it's my job to like speak to them in
a way that allows them to feel
comfortable enough to share information
and I and I speak differently to
different people what is this right now
you tell me Bonnie I don't know I don't
know your different ways this is me
feeling comfortable around you that I
can share my secrets and fear and hopes
and fears with an audience that may not
have known this information about me but
yeah what is the biggest problem with
financial I asked you that question I
also put that down okay all right great
minds think it like ladies first um I
think this is from my experience I don't
know about um news in Canada or us but
in Taiwan I feel like a lot of news are
copying each other and they are executed
by a lot of interns that don't know know
what they're talking about they don't
know what the news is about they copy
and paste they would probably pull out
some other
information and because their kpi is
either reach click or views they would
put down something that they think the
viewers want to see for example the
market crashed like 80% or like Trump
did this or that you know something that
touches the human psychology like you
just want to click but does do you
really learn something from it not
necessarily but because their manager or
their bosses want like their kpi should
be hey I want to see your growth over a
year or like two years instead they want
the report every day like how how many
clicks or how many views did you get
today I see what you mean they so yeah
they're shortterm thinkers they air on
the side of being too Sensational I know
exactly what you mean and so they're
bonus is dependent on the clicks they
get this month so I don't think the
problem is the intern or the staff it's
the bosses see sometimes I sacrifice
clicks for Quality conversation yes
because I know a specific guest will not
get me a lot of clicks Eugene fma's
interview with me probably one of the
most in influential things I've done in
my
career less than 50,000
views but you know if my only metric was
clicks I wouldn't have aired that right
so let me ask you this now I have an
answer to that myself s is what makes
you think people click on AUM thumbnail
where a headline generally speaking okay
any channel whether you're Mr Beast or
your you know Bonnie blockchain M why do
people click there are so many reasons
every every time they click they get
what they wanted right then the next
time when this shows up they want to
click again because they know okay I'm
getting this you know standard you won't
give me some today so it's
consistency but what are let's say some
ingredients that thumbnails that that go
into a successful thumbnail oh just I
have two but I'll ask you first itself
yeah
colors okay font
okay size oh sorry I don't mean
thumbnail I mean just the title not the
image the title yeah oh the title even
though I I've been told thumbnail is
more important because that's what
people see first but
yeah the title has to
ask a question that they want an answer
to that's good yeah okay yours I think
people click for one of two reasons one
the title elicits an emotional response
either it's happiness or fear it's like
oh markets are down it's crashing I'm
afraid of losing my money so I want to
click on it and find out so I'm afraid
or number two uh it presents new
information that maybe I didn't know
before the best thumbnails do twoo mhm
two things both of those things it's it
elicits an emotional response and also
gives you new information markets are
down because
Trump you know abandoned Ukraine okay
that's that's two things right now I'm
afraid of markets crashing but now I'm
also not sure why Trump did that so now
I'm curious to click on it that's just
an example but you're giving the answer
in the thumbnail Market is crashing
because yeah I've I've thought about
this a lot should I give the answer in
the thumbnail I don't have a definitive
answer sometimes it's yes sometimes it's
no it really depends on the topic I find
that a lot of times stating the fact or
the just giving it away is actually more
powerful let me give you an example is
there gold in Fort Knox I'm just off the
top of my head there's an audit going on
Elon mus wants to audit Fort Knox he
wants to find out how much gold there is
is there gold in Fort Knox Elon musk's
Doge reveals that's that's a good thumb
that's a good title I would click on
that
counter that okay
because people when you upload that
video people already know the answer if
they're interested in this if it's a yes
or no people already know like people
who are interested in this that's why I
don't like yes no questions as why yes
you're right yeah so like it has to be
something that they have not thought
about so let's suppose they don't find
in this I'm just making it up let's
suppose they don't find gold there
bombshell report there's no golden four
KNX see I just gave the answer away but
now I think you're more inclined to
click on the second one because because
now you now it's like this dramatic
piece of information that you want to
know more about I would add but they
found this oh okay but they'll be like
you know something something interesting
about Chinese media I've noticed you can
fit more information in the title
because every word is its own character
and you have a character limit of 100
characters I don't know if it's true
yeah sure but you you are able to add
what you just said because you have
higher character well no you have the
same character count but you have more
information to fit in because every
Chinese word is maybe two three
characters Max and so you can fit more
ideas into the title but whereas in
English words are words are like one
word is like 10 characters right so you
can you're constrained by the number of
ideas you put in the title so already
Chinese creators are at an advantage I
tend to think it's easier in English cuz
Okay you know how like Financial
channels they always say do this now in
Chinese you can't really say
that like that's very strange first of
all you're never supposed to do that cuz
that's Financial advice and that but
what I'm saying is you know you can the
emotions that you said you want to
trigger if you say do this now or like
you got to know like three things you
have to know it's very hard to express
that in
Chinese maybe but going back to your
example of stating a piece of
information M you can fit more
information true because you have um
more words you can fit into the 100
character limit that's something I
noticed as soon as I started watching
your channel I was like the first I
can't read Chinese very well so I'm like
copy pasting into Google translate and
then Google Translate is giving me like
this like like 50-word translation I'm
like there's no way I could the first
thought is there's no way I could fit
this into my own title true true and
then I thought about it I was like yo
it's because Bonnie's channel is in
Chinese and you can fit more Concepts
not even words but Concepts into the
title and so when a Chinese viewer is
scanning it like really quickly it's
like already their brain is processing
more information that is very
interesting yes yes and sometimes you
know because viewers spent I don't know
half a second looking at your title and
they decide within half a second if they
want to click on it so you cannot add
too many Concepts it has to be yeah just
enough I've been told 50 characters is
the
optimal but I I don't know you had
comments about Chinese subtitles I did
yeah I I was it's a culture shock to me
how everybody in Taiwan watches media
with subtitles yes um I mean I I know
subtitles help mhm but even in chines
not just English yeah yeah I I I know
like you know you watch like Taiwanese
TV anything yeah game shows drama news
yeah and I'm just like how do they have
time for this like how how do they do
this because especially with news
channels like they need a faster
turnaround time MH it's like how do you
anyway they must be working around the
clock and it's not something I'm used to
cuz you know in North America we don't
have subtitles on everything we do it on
our shorts for like social media because
well the obvious reason is you can't
listen if you're on the train or
whatever you work and so you have to
look at it and also it keeps your
attention SP but like you watch anything
on American TV there's no subtitles
unless you are watching Netflix and you
select subtitles
buture I know CU it takes so much time
that's the bottleneck for you it is
because in Chinese if people don't know
one word
one pronunciation can mean a thousand
different things yeah and you have to
manually select which word like it's
terrible terrible as in for people
that's trying to type subtitles within a
short period of time mhm of course
there's Ai and stuff but right now ai in
Chinese it still sounds
very robot is MH like people don't
actually talk like that so the subtitles
and stuff like I wanted to be as natural
as possible so just typing subtitles I
used to type my own subtitles how long
did it take you for each video that it
would take like 6
hours crazy you had an interesting
question you sent to me mhm quantity
versus quality yes I'm curious to I have
an answer but I'm curious to get your
take um I think quantity is at least
once a week that but quality is more
important cuz you see a lot of big
channels they don't upload that often
but when they do people will watch it
yeah because they know hey I'm getting
something out of this yeah so for me if
I had had to pick one mhm of course yeah
yeah yeah but you have to see this is an
interesting question because you're
assuming they're mutually exclusive you
have to have one or the other for many
channels it is you're right yeah Stalin
I like quotes Joseph Stalin had a
quote there you
go how are you able to talk to me for an
hour so much patience B quantity is a
quality in itself
oh think about that do you just write
those quotes down I I have a lot of
random stuff floating in my head
wow true I agree yeah but for people who
solo like YouTube they don't have a team
I guess you kind of have to you publish
as much as you need to right so this is
the way I think about growing my company
cuz you went back to how did I grow so
fast actually I could have grown faster
um but anyway the only metric I care
about is watch hours over a month views
but more specifically watch hours
because people can click a lot but if
they don't watch a lot you know your
your attention is low your watch hour is
still low it doesn't matter so what is
watch hours it's just a number number of
hours that has been accumulated on your
channel over a period of time let's take
a month for example hour that is the
only driver that I think drives the
valuation of a media company because
your sponsors care about how many views
they get um your your audience your main
kpi being watch hours will determine how
popular your content is and how long
your audience is watching your show for
MH and then you can adjust your strategy
that way your growth rate and how many
people you need to hire are dependent on
the watch hours you want to Target for
for a certain month so what are the
variables that determine watch hours
it's just two things really break down
the math your total watch hours equals
the number of unique visitors on your
channel times the average amount of time
each visitor watches so knowing that you
have two ways to grow your channel you
can either focus on the number of people
watching or the amount of time people
watch your show or your channel overall
not just one show but your channel
overall the second variable I think is
easier to control that's just a simple
function of quantity if you publish more
videos that are obviously not like crap
every day but like things that are
aligned with your audience's
interest the more you publish the more
watch hours you will accumulate just by
the number of people let's say you 100
viewers right everybody watches one hour
a day your total watch hours over 30
days is 30 * 1 but let's say you all of
a sudden double your content now you
have 2 hours of content every day the
same assuming this is a big assumption
assuming you have the same audience who
is able to watch your show now they're
watching two hours per day 2 * 10 time
30 that's 600 hours per month you've
just doubled your watch hours so there's
there's there's a diminishing marginal
returns after a while right so you
finding that optimal I don't know what
that is yet but you do have diminishing
marginal utility after a certain P Peri
perod of time after a certain number of
videos I believe that number is maybe
three or four but I haven't maxed that
out yet three or four a day a day and
you well in your assumption people who
used to watch you for an hour a day they
would watch for three hours now yes or
they will watch a little bit of this a
little bit of that a little bit of that
really the total accumulation would be
different so here's the second part the
first part of the equation is the number
of people you can't get one person to
watch your show for 6 hours a day nobody
would do that right let's say you
publish six times a day
yous why you have toow your audience so
that some's interested in cpto some's
interested in someone's interested in
real estate you have different people
watching different content throughout
the day are you considering how
algorithm work I don't really know what
the algorithm is it changes every like I
don't know it changes all the time so I
don't really think about it as much
there are some metrics that are
consistent so in terms of importance so
audience retention is one of them MH
right we talked about that um I think
audience retention I think about I think
click through rate yes is another really
important that's thumbnail click through
rate is thumbnail audience retention is
just the quality of your videos those
are really the only two metrics that
really matter what I heard is they first
push the content to people that
subscribe to you that always watches
your and then if they click if most
people click then they'll push it to a
wider audience yeah that's why you find
when your video reach like a big amount
of views your your click-through rate is
actually lower because YouTube pushes
the content to people that don't usually
watch Finance stuff for example or your
clickthrough rate drops over time drops
over time but that doesn't mean it's bad
yeah it just means YouTube pushes it to
people that's interesting that weren't
familiar with you you should aim for a
high initial click-through rate is what
you're saying initial yes but then later
on on if I look at my Channel all the
videos with the highest views their
clickthrough rate is not the best okay
is because I believe YouTube actually
push these two that is possible a new
group of audience that is possible
especially for finance not everyone's
interested in finance and so if it
pushes to a large audience there will be
people who won't click on it you're
right I notice your videos more than
mine have a longer shelf life meaning
you'll post something like let's say 3
days ago
it would get maybe 20,000 views the
first day and then like I check a week
later I'm like holy how's it 12,000 how
did that happen like do you H H how do
you do that because with interviews I
think it's also because I need time to
add subtitles and do the editing sure I
don't want to talk about what's
happening right now I want to talk about
like your philosophy like it something
that can last for a long time so even if
I click on this video a year later I can
still learn from
yeah you have a different approach than
me because I because I can't because I
right now I cannot make like a video a
day so see you see that this is an
example of a good Creator because you
know your own constraints and then
you you you you tailor your content
around your constraints whereas let's
say hypothetically if you had a team of
20 people right and your expenses were
not a
concern you could in theory film all day
6 hours a day or whatever you could live
stream you could do a lot of things you
could have a mix of Evergreen content
plus current news that you live stream
you know you can have everything right
right so if I remove the production
constraint you could do all of it but
right now because you have that
constraint you're focusing on Evergreen
content but I also think if I only talk
about current events that like why don't
they just watch news because that's even
faster than me for sure like I can't
beat CNBC
yeah you can you can live stream it well
okay I'm not trying to play that game
I'm not trying
to like beat the traditional media
because you are beating CNBC in many
respects because people follow creators
like you now that is because you talk
about a whole different thing like they
feel like they can relate to you like
the questions you ask because I feel
like on CNBC or like Bloomberg they
cannot ask dumb questions but here I can
I'm like I'm a dumbass tell me about
yourself you know what I mean you are
also a viewer when I'm interviewing you
I'm learning something from you and I'm
imagining like thinking like oh what
what would the viewers want like what
would they want to ask so I'm asking
that too yeah you yeah you could pull
the viewers this is one of the
advantages of our of channels like us is
that we can engage with our viewers
directly through tweets Community posts
whatever I don't know Discord you can
ask people what they want to hear you
can lcit questions by email which is
what I do and then you can just ask
questions that your community want to
hear whereas if you're mainstream like
CNBC and Bloomberg you don't really have
that option as at least not on a daily
basis so I think there's a little bit of
Disconnect when you're really really big
and that's one of the things that you
have to be aware of when you get bigger
in scale which you will I'm Bing on a
million views sorry a million
subscribers for Bonnie and by next year
I'll try so once you get even bigger
than you are now you will have I believe
you will have the issue of becoming more
distant with your audience because you
can't relate to a million people so it's
like how do you make everyone happy the
answer is you
don't and so you know the bigger you get
the more disconnect I find you get with
your audience and so you have to find
other ways to engage them other ways to
talk to them other ways to interact with
your audience which is why I I'm pushing
towards more live streaming because you
can actually get comments live and when
you say disconnect why what do you mean
making content that I want versus
content that the audience wants but that
means you grew not the media company you
grew as a person well we're always
growing as people I'm just there's
always topics that I may find
interesting that other people won't
right and so I just don't talk about
that but as I grow bigger and I have to
cover more things there's some people
I'll alienate and then other people I
won't and so it's like okay how do I
make everyone happy this is my question
when I grow bigger and my solution to
that is actually quantity because I can
create gold content Bitcoin content and
stocks content three times a day so the
gold people will watch that the Bitcoin
people will watch that yeah what I find
myself doing is you know like I said I
like to ask questions right but as you
grow in the industry for example if I
learn if now I'm like a defi Dean like I
know everything about defi sometimes if
I'm interviewing a person that is also a
deun I'll just hear why you pointing at
me I'll just hear what you say and in my
head it will not spark a question
because you just naturally think
everybody should understand that already
that is you growing right but then every
time I try to drag myself back to wait
hold on I know this because I spent so
much time on this but then for a person
that just got into crypto or Finance
they don't know what this
means just as like as simple as like a
futures a lot of people you think people
know what it is but I think most people
don't the hard part for our for us is
explaining what that is in a way that
not only is easy to understand
but interesting for
somebody and it's interesting for
different people right a concept is you
need to explain it differently to
different people in order for them to
relate to you right so let's say what is
money for a 90-year-old they want to
know how to protect their wealth and how
to reti
so then you explain Concepts like that
you explain to a 5e how many Pokemon
cards can you buy right you have to exp
make a video that reaches everybody you
can't that's what I'm trying to say
understand your demographic understand
your audience and then cater it that way
you can't reach everyone in the same
video what you can do is make sub
channels or different channels or
different videos within the same channel
targeting different audiences but in one
video you can't but you can try to reach
as many people as you can yes if your
goal is to have a broad-based audience
that is not just crypto Focus then you
then yeah you have to think of questions
that are more appealing to other people
who may not be investing crypto or in my
case because I'm not a crypto focused
Channel like maybe you I try to explain
crypto Concepts a little bit like more
as an economist and not so deep which is
where you would come in like you would
you know get in a little bit deeper I
ask my mom or I don't ask her she
watches every video of mine multiple
times and she would tell me she
understands what I'm talking about she
ask you if you understand no I would oh
you ask her no I would ask her yeah okay
what did she say if it's like over 70%
it's a good video because she doesn't
know anything about crypto well I I
would hope that she does now but you
know like she's a mom not really don't
really care about digital assets and
think it's very dangerous and stuff if
she understands 70% and she's like oh I
learned this and that it's a good video
what is her what is her number usually
50 70 80 no she she would
say like only a few here and there she
doesn't understand that's good yeah so
you're yeah that's I I would agree with
her because you explain things in a way
that I think that's what makes your
channel popular is you explain difficult
Concepts in an easy to understand way or
approachable which is very hard to do
because you yourself have to really
understand it yes before you're able B
to do that
yes yeah so yeah there is a constraint
because you KN you do more homework than
most other people so you spend more time
on every video but it works out because
like I said maybe you spend less time on
a video than some other channels I I
believe you spend a lot more time per
video than me I think that I I I believe
that but your engagement rate is higher
I'm pretty sure if I looked in your
analytics that would support my theory I
grow by Brute Force you grow because you
you target your engagement I think
so I'm recruiting my troop yeah
absolutely yeah so what's going to get
you to a million subscribers how do you
do that what's your next what's your
next uh step here just to make more
videos more high quality videos cuz I I
do my own research but so I want to
focus my time on
that so I can't really go that deep into
the production anymore if I want to make
more
videos yeah right now like I
still wash all the edits and stuff like
if if there's any you had to grow your
team who would you hire next what kind
of role would you hire next social media
manager that okay yeah you know just
kind of go through everything with the
editors yeah that role okay MH all right
what would you say to yourself if you
could go back to when you first started
start at YouTube oh uh that wasn't my
own channel that was a long time ago um
not your own channel my own channel uh
you mean like mistakes I've made or
could be or you could be like good job
you're great I never tell myself that I
my my only competitor in my field is
myself from a month ago I know that
sounds very cheesy that is the only
Benchmark so you put up with me for 90
minutes put up with me now I'm just
throwing every cliche at the book but
it's it's true though Bonnie I don't
care what other people are doing I
should have probably
hired
sooner I was very conservative with by
cash at the beginning I could have grown
faster I think that's probably the only
thing I would change because I didn't
start hiring editors and producers until
six seven months in oh wait so you used
to edit your own stuff everything I did
myself wow okay see I'm not that
talented so I don't know how to edit
well you're talented in other ways I
mean I set up my own camera but I
literally was filming in my mother's
spare bedroom for the first six seven
months because I didn't know when I
would make money so I moved back with my
mom after my after I quit my job and I
had my it was like a spare room like
this she had a room and I just set up my
cameras and I set up my workstation I
edited everything myself it was the
first couple months was rough it was
like 14 hour day seven days a week um I
had enough cash flow to to hire people
within 4 months but I was still a little
bit like conservative still so I didn't
make my first hire until 7 months um
knowing what I know now I could have
just spent my cash a little bit sooner I
would have grown faster that's because
now you know you can actually make money
yes in the beginning I wasn't sure but
even when I was making money I wasn't
sure if I could keep making money
because you know YouTubers they come and
go all the time I was like okay it's my
third month of being net positive I was
still living I could have moved out I
was still living at home I was like okay
what do I do with my cash is my uh
question that I asked first thing I did
was hire an editor second thing was move
out and get my own
rent and then I grew my team after that
nice nice
um if I couldn't answer the same
question i' would probably
say think longterm like I was worried
about the cash flow at first as well I
was but you know now now looking back
like if you told me in my first month of
youtubing you if you say hey one day
you're going to work with let's say
Michael sailor or like even binance and
all that sure yeah I would be like what
are you talking about but then now you
actually work with these people and it's
like your dayto day don't you feel that
way like don't I would tell myself not
to worry that
much well what were you worried about no
worry as in like oh oh uh is this going
to work and and I wasn't worried like I
couldn't live my life I was just like
should I go all in cuz I have I had a
job at the time yeah this is my question
for you cuz you told me offline you had
a job yes at another Media company and
then you started your own YouTube
channel as a side hustle right yeah at
what point did you think I could do this
full-time when I started feeling like
because when I started it didn't not
feel like I don't go around tell people
I'm a YouTuber right cuz it's like such
a new role mhm but then later on after I
think half a year a year I was very
comfortable this is my main thing now MH
like the TV host and all that I don't
even feel like I'm proud to tell you I
do that mhm I'm more happier sharing
that I'm doing this crypto YouTube that
is when I'm like oh it's time it wasn't
like I've made enough money now I can do
myself I
mean YouTube itself I mean there has to
be a point where it's like your YouTube
was higher than your salary and so it
was net negative for you to stay at your
last job no no no no it wasn't like that
it wasn't like that okay no um cuz I
haven't you know like the sponsorship
Google ad is very little so I don't even
look at that sure um
sponsorship I think the first for the
longest time I did not have sponsorship
came much later yeah so that oh so
sponsorship came after you quit your
last job I can't remember the exact
timeline but I wasn't counting on that I
see yeah and when your channel is small
like the sponsorship money is so you
took an even bigger risk than me I don't
know but I had my tsmc so I wasn't
worried I wasn't that worried I mean I
was
worried basically I was rich so I didn't
really care you know if this that's it
you have to have as an investor it's
like I have enough cash so if something
fails it's okay but you still you still
want to be successful so I was like she
humble bragging this
girl no what I was trying to say is I
was still definitely worried about cash
flow are you kidding me see for me I
took I believe I took a smaller risk
than you even though I quit my job first
why is that smaller risk because I had
an audience already in the finance space
you had no
your related people didn't Bon CH you
whatever you were doing so you are have
you have a completely different audience
now yeah than maybe before so you
started literally from zero I didn't
start from zero I us I used to have 90%
female watching me what is it now 90
watching me as in like my my previous
work oh okay it was about like traveling
and all that like the girly stuff
variety show it was 90% girls now it's I
think 80 something per that makes sense
yeah yeah you're in a male dominated
field yeah see my very first video on my
YouTube channel you can see on my oldest
video had 140,000 views or
something wow that's because I have an
audience already that's what I'm saying
did you like tell people you're going to
this new channel I also have Twitter I
have a Twitter account I mean I don't
have a huge Twitter uh following I me
but it was enough to draw the audience
um and I or before my first video I
already had 2,000 subscribers just
people
waiting that so that algorithm kind of
helped the first video was already
pushed to 2,000 people and then it got
pushed to more people yeah within my
first video got 10,000 subscribers
within the first week I got 30,000
subscribers anyway the point I'm making
is I already had an audience so it was
less Point making
is no that's you that's you you're the
queen of humble pranks
okay okay well I see but if I had done
let's say I the reverse right let's say
I went from Finance to Lifestyle I would
be from zero so that I wouldn't do that
yeah why did I even do that well that
was the first question I asked you but
what really motivates you like right now
because you you're you're successful you
have cash flow you you have your tsmc
you know you know it's like you're
retired it's fine but I'm not retired
but like you could I'm just saying why
are you still doing what you're doing
cuz I still need to learn a lot more
like there's so many interesting people
out there it okay hold on so there's
learning and then there's producing
content you could learn by yourself by
watching videos reading whatever you
just do that by yourself be a private
investor be a private person don't you
think it's cool to be able to talk to
who whoever you
want yes is that why you do it that is
one of the reasons
okay like I could just talk to David
Lynn how great is that I mean yeah I i'
be very liit you're very lucky Bonnie
I'd be very limited
interviews but that too and also like a
lot to learn and also people say well
Financial Freedom is not a set number
it's always adjusting as you go right so
I can't retire yet would there be a
point where you would stop I don't think
so so this is this is your career for
life I would hope YouTube will be around
for the next well I mean it's not just
youtubing it could be another platform
right but you would keep Broadcasting
because this is interesting like I'm
having fun I don't feel like I'm working
you found your purpose in
life did you have like a I don't like to
use all these big words it gives me like
this chill okay like my purpose and my
goal I yeah I ask people about those
questions but I don't yeah see it's
difficult being interviewed right yeah
it's harder being interviewed than
interviewing I find yes yeah so you
don't like the questions you ask that's
that's good that means questions are
hard sufficiently difficult what is your
purpose in life yeah it's to educate as
many people as I can about finance and
economics but do you not feel like your
purpose changes as you grow definitely I
didn't have a purpose for a long time
now I find found one maybe my purpose
will change in the future maybe my
purpose will be to take care of my
family I don't know but my career Focus
will always be purpose will be
to the the word I hate the word
influence because that doesn't mean see
we're doing the same thing I don't like
purpose and like educate and but I do
want to educate people because I think
there's a lot of there's a lot of power
in educating people that's why I really
like teachers I really respect teachers
School teach they should get paid more
they do in Scandinavia but yes in the US
and everywhere else they should um and I
think a lot of and it's so powerful what
we can do which is to educate people
online for free people can watch a
Bonnie video for free and learn about
whatever right you know um that was not
possible 20 years ago you have to go to
school you have to pay
money go to the library I would like to
think I'm learning with them instead of
educating them because do you feel like
you need to leave a legacy before you
die no you don't have that
ambition can I give you another quote or
am I out of oh man give it to me do I
have a quote quot oh man I don't I can't
remember who said this but I like this
quote we die three times oh my God
confucious no no not confucious what do
you
it's confus you know what the qu do you
know what the quote is we die three okay
no no you what do you what do you think
I want to say no no what do you think I
was going to say no something about like
you start living when you realize you're
whatever no you die three times the
first is when your body dies oh the
second is when you're put in the grave
the third is the last time your name is
spoken okay come on that's a little too
like dark I want to live forever you yes
you want to live forever but do you do
you really think after you pass you care
about if people are still talking about
you absolutely except for your family
yeah like I want my family to talk about
me but one day your family will pass
then what then it's
fine at that point I probably don't care
anymore well you physically can't care
yes exactly but what you do in life mhm
should have an influence in eternity do
you not think that it what you do in
life should still matter in your death
do you not think that no I do think that
but eventually it will pass unless
you're like super successful maybe maybe
but that's we define success differently
right yeah for me success is simply long
after me and everyone I know now are
gone MH people will still talk about my
work in some way because it's still on
YouTube sure
it's on the internet the internet
doesn't die exactly but you think about
the people who have built Society we
still talk about them long after their
dead not all of them are super rich not
all of them are super famous across
worlds but everything you see around the
world everything you see in your life
was created by somebody and there's
always some influence that those people
have had even after they're dead that's
what I want to be in
media so I love that thank you bigger
purpose yeah I think there's always a
bigger purpose than yourself in life and
yeah we're doing something in New York
together yes we are what are we doing
there's a great conference hosted by
blockworks great Media Company digital
assets Summit March 18th to 20th and uh
I invited Bonnie to co-host with me yes
because uh Bonnie is awesome
oh thanks and we're going to be
interviewing people together some really
really cool people yeah some really cool
people people can check out the speakers
list I won't reveal any names yet but
people should just tune in to our
channels later in March they can just
look at the web page and see the biggest
names yeah there's some yeah there's
some there's some very influential
people not just in crypto but also um
fintech economics it's just I've done
this a long time and this is probably
the best guest list that we've put
together um in my career so I'm really
excited about that I'm really excited
you're joining us yeah super excited
this is the first time I joined like a
conference in us I think yeah the first
time I met people in crypto outside of
Chinese speaking region was the sailor
party I think okay I met you guys right
and then this is going to be the second
time I join any event of course is this
the first time you've filmed at a
conference yes you've lot of interviews
at a conference okay I also don't really
go to conferences yeah yeah and is this
the first time you've collaborated with
another YouTube channel doing interviews
at this scale for sure okay so a lot of
first for you yeah so what are you most
looking forward to just all these people
I used to you know read on the news I
can actually talk to them like it's
great cool this is one of the perks of
our job we get to meet cool people and
you're right about the list cuz a lot of
times look at the guest list you're like
oh there are a few that are really big
but you know this time it's you see all
the names you're familiar with I felt a
little intimidated personally by who by
all these people that were talking to
how do you feel that way I mean do you
do you cope with that somehow I haven't
started thinking about it you will yeah
I'm going to start feeling the stress
you know how this collects your data
it's okay we'll work on it together
okay thank you David thank you Bonnie
it's fun